In this video, we're going to take a look at Claude's latest feature, Agent Teams.And first of all, we're going to take a look at what is Agent Teams, and what is the difference between sub-agents and the Agent Teams, what problem does Agent Teams try to solve, and then we're going to dive into how to set this up on your local machine, how we can be able to use Tmax here to basically view all the Agent Teams members here inside of one terminal sessions, inside of Claude code.
在這支影片中，我們將探討 Claude 最新的功能——Agent Teams。首先，我們會介紹什麼是 Agent Teams，以及子代理與 Agent Teams 的差別，Agent Teams 試圖解決什麼問題，然後我們會深入探討如何在你的本地機器上設定這個功能， 我們如何利用 tmux 基本上在一個終端機會話中，透過 Claude Code 查看所有 Agent Teams 成員。
And that's, we're also going to take a look at how to start a project, how to manage it, how do we interact with each agents, how do we communicate it, and be able to eventually complete the projects.going to take a look at how to convert this into a claw scale so that we can be able to reuse it in the future.So pretty much that's what we cover in this video and if you're interested let's get into it.Alright so before we jump in a quick intro for those who are new here.
我們也會探討如何啟動專案、如何管理、如何與每位代理人互動、如何溝通，並最終能夠完成專案。我們會探討如何將此轉換成 Claude skill，以便未來能重複使用。所以這支影片大致涵蓋了這些，如果你有興趣，我們來深入探討。好了，在我們開始之前，先簡單介紹一下，給剛來這裡的人。
My name is Eric and I spent years as a senior software engineer at companies like Amazon, AWS and Microsoft and I have started this channel to share everything that I learned along the way from AI encoding to automationsweb3, career developments, and more, all broken down into practical tutorials that you can actually follow.And of course, we also have a school community where you can get access to all the resources.templates, plus our community supports.So if you're ready to level up, make sure to check out my YouTube channel and hit that subscribe button.
我叫 Eric，曾在 Amazon、AWS 和 Microsoft 等公司擔任資深軟體工程師多年，我開設這個頻道是想分享我一路上學到的一切，從 AI 編碼到自動化 web3、職涯發展等等，全部拆解成實用的教學，讓你真正能跟著做。當然，我們也有學校社群，你可以在那裡取得所有資源模板，以及我們的社群支援。所以如果你準備好升級，記得去我的 YouTube 頻道看看並點擊訂閱按鈕。
Now let's get back to the video.Alright, so to get started, first thing first, I want to topple the difference between agent teams, sub-agents, and default mode.So now let's take this as an example, right?Let's say you're a developer here, you're trying to write the UI component for the upload, the server-side for the edge functions, building the matching algorithm, and writing a test, right?That's basically your task, and what happened here is that you're using a default mode,One agent only has one context window.
現在讓我們回到影片。好，首先我想釐清 Agent Teams、子代理和預設模式之間的差異。現在我們拿這個當作例子，好嗎？假設你是這裡的開發者，你正在嘗試撰寫上傳的 UI 元件、Edge 函式的伺服器端元件、建立匹配演算法，並撰寫測試，對吧？這基本上就是你的任務，而這裡發生的情況是你用的是預設模式，一個代理只有一個上下文視窗。
So if you're going to complete a task with one agent, you will basically complete this task sequentially, which means that you first write the upload UI component, write the SuperBase Edge functions to handle this, building the matching algorithms and writing tests sequentially one after the other.Now, this approach might be slow, but the other problem that is very severe is that the higher the context, the lower the accuracy, which means that as the task getting more complex and the context window start to fill up, the accuracy start to get lower, and that's really what the sub-agent
所以如果你要用一個代理完成任務，基本上就是依序完成，也就是說你先寫上傳介面元件，寫 Supabase Edge 函式來處理這個，然後依序建立匹配演算法，然後依序寫測試。這種方法可能比較慢，但另一個非常嚴重的問題是，上下文越高，準確度越低，這表示隨著任務越來越複雜、上下文視窗逐漸填滿，準確度也會下降，這正是子代理的重點
really try to solve is that we're trying to reduce the complexity for each agent by having multiple sub-agents here running at the same time.So given the same task, for example, writing the UI, the edge functions, and building the matching algorithms and writing a test, right?We can literally divide this work into multiple sub-agents where one agent focuses on the UI, the other one is focusing on the backend, the other one is focusing on the matching algorithm.
真正想解決的是，我們試圖透過同時執行多個子代理來降低每個代理的複雜度。所以給我同樣的任務，例如寫介面、邊緣函數、建立匹配演算法並撰寫測試，對吧？我們可以將這項工作分成多個子代理，其中一個專注於使用者介面，另一個專注於後端，另一個專注於匹配演算法。
And pretty much we can have the main context window here as become an orchestrator, but divide task into multiple sub-agents, therefore we have lesscontext window for each subagent right here.But the problem here is that there's no communication between different subagents.For example, let's say we have the subagent #1, building the UI for the uploader, and it has defined the data types for that.And let's say we have our sub-agent number two here building the edge functions, and it has also defined the data types for that as well.
基本上我們可以把主要的上下文視窗設為編排器，但將任務拆分成多個子代理，因此每個子代理的上下文視窗較少。但問題在於不同子代理之間沒有溝通。舉例來說，假設我們有子代理 #1，正在建立上傳者的使用者介面，並且它已經定義了該資料型態。假設我們有第二個子代理正在建立 Edge 函式，並且它也定義了這些 Edge 函式的資料型態。
But because there's no communication between the sub-agents, they have no idea if the types that it defines in the frontend is aligned with the backend.And what happened then is that after the task is completed, they run the applications, they realize that the types checks are different, then it got an error, right?Because there's no communication on what the sub-agent one does that sub-agent two have to know about.So that's what the core issue that the agent team here is trying to solve, where now you can see that we have our agent team,
但因為子代理之間沒有溝通，他們根本不知道前端定義的類型是否與後端對齊。接著任務完成後，他們執行應用程式，發現檢查類型不同，然後就出現錯誤，對吧？因為沒有溝通，關於子代理一做了什麼，而子代理二必須知道。這就是 Agent Teams 想要解決的核心問題，現在你可以看到我們的 Agent Teams，
and the team leader here will basically spend multiple sub-agents and what's going to happen here is that for each sub-agent, it can be able to communicate with each other.For example, after the backend sub-agents here complete the job, it will basically send the data types that it creates to the frontend sub-agents and the frontend sub-agent here will take that types that the backend creates and be able to define the types in the frontend as well.So that there's no miscommunication and no misalignment between different sub-agents work.
而這裡的Team Lead基本上會分配多個子代理，而這裡會發生的是，每個子代理之間都能互相溝通。舉例來說，當後端子代理完成工作後，它會將建立的資料型態傳送給前端子代理，前端子代理會接收後端建立的類型，並能在前端定義這些類型。這樣不同子代理的工作就不會有誤會或不協調。
And clearly you can see that this is the benefits of agent teams is that we have a shared communications between all the sub-agents that we have.And to summarize everything, basically the defaultagent here has only one context window, some agents here have isolated contacts but cannot talk to each other, and the agent teams on the other hand can be able to enable like full parallel collaborations between multiple agents, and multiple agents here can directly communicate to each agent right here.So pretty much that's the difference between those three modes instead of claw code.
很明顯，你可以看到Agent Teams的好處是，我們所有子代理之間有共享的溝通。總結來說，基本上這裡的 default agent 只有一個上下文視窗，有些代理有獨立的上下文視窗但無法彼此溝通，而Agent Teams則能實現多個代理之間的完全平行協作，且多個代理可以直接與每位代理溝通。所以基本上這就是在 Claude Code 中這三種模式的差別。
Alright, so now you know the difference, let's take a look at how we can be able to set this up on our local machine, but first thing first we're going to do here is to make sure that we have the latest version in our claw code in our local machine.So what we're going to do here is I'm just going to jump back to my terminal.No matter if you're in a project or in a brand new terminal in the root directory, all you have to do here is just do clod updates.
好了，現在你知道差別了，讓我們來看看如何在本地機器上設定，但首先我們要確保本地機器的 Claude Code 版本是最新版本。所以我們現在要做的是，我要跳回我的終端機。不管你是在專案中，還是在根目錄的新終端機裡，這裡你只要執行 Claude 更新就行了。
And this will basically update the current version to the latest version that we have in our clod code.It's just going to check for updates with the latest version.And here you can see that it will basically update my clod code with the latest version, which you can see that we have that updated already.So next thing we're going to do here is basically try to set up the configurations and the Tmax.
這基本上會將目前的版本更新到我們 Claude Code 中擁有的最新版本。它只是會檢查最新版本的更新。你可以看到它基本上會用最新版本更新我的 Claude Code，你也可以看到我們已經有更新了。接下來我們要做的是嘗試設定配置和 tmux。
And Tmax is basically trying to do here is basically a way for you to create multiple terminal windows here inside of your terminal so that you can be able to have communications with different agentsindividually with its own terminal windows.Now so in this case to install this what we're going to do here is just going to do brew install and we're just going to do type in tmax and we're just going to hit enter and we'll basically install this using homebrew.
而 tmux 基本上就是讓你在終端機內建立多個終端視窗，這樣你就能用自己的終端視窗與不同的代理進行通訊。現在，在這裡安裝這個，我們要做的是 brew 安裝，然後在 tmux 裡輸入，然後按下 enter，基本上就是用 homebrew 來安裝。
Okay so now you can see that we have this successfully installed and after we have this installed here you can see this is where we can have our display mode which the agent teams here supports two display modes.One is in progress where we're going to have one terminal sessions using shift and up/down or key to basically select which teammates we wanted to communicate with or the other way we can do is to have
現在你可以看到我們已經成功安裝了這個模式，安裝完成後你可以看到這裡是顯示模式，這裡的 Agent Teams 支援兩種顯示模式。其中一種是在進行中，我們會用 shift 和 up/down 或 key 來選擇想要溝通的隊友，進行一個終端會話;另一種方式是
a split panels and basically what's going to happen is you can see everyone's output at once by clicking on the section to interact with it using Tmax.Okay, that's why I'm trying to use Tmax here inside of Clawcode.Alright, so now to basically enable the Tmax here inside of Clawcode, all we have to do here is just run this command in the root directory.
分割面板，基本上你會透過點擊 tmux 互動的區塊，同時看到所有人的輸出。好，這就是為什麼我嘗試在 Claude Code 裡面使用 tmux。好，現在要在 Claude Code 裡啟用 tmux，我們只要在根目錄執行這個指令就好。
So now I'm just going to open a terminal right here and basically paste that command and what's going to happen here is basically going to enable the Clawcode agent teams mode to be true and also the Tmax split panels here to be true as well.So here I'm just going to enter this and we basically have those settings
現在我會在這裡開啟一個終端機，基本上貼上那個指令，接下來會讓 Claude Code 的 Agent Teams 模式變成 true，這裡的 tmux 分割面板也變成 true。所以我現在就輸入這個，基本上就是這些設定
set in place all right so now what we can do here is basically start our Tmax new sessions with Claude so what we can do is we're just going to run this command right here and I'll make sure to put this inside of our school community so you can get access to this entire guide inside of our video resource so all we have to do here is I'm going to first cd into my desktop and cd into my bookkeeping applications
設置好了。現在我們可以開始用 Claude 進行 tmux 的新工作階段。我們會在這裡執行這個指令，我會確保把它放進我們的學校社群裡，讓你能在我們的影片資源中取得完整指南，我們只需要先 cd 進入我的桌面，再 cd 進入我的記帳應用程式
And then what's going to happen, I'm just going to paste that command right here for Tmax new sessions.So currently I'm inside of the project I'm trying to build.And simply I'm just going to run this command right here.And you can see that this is what we have.So we're inside of Tmax mode.And now what we're going to do here is basically try to run Claude with the dangerously skip permissions.And I'm just going to have a Claude sessions inside of the Tmax mode.
接著會發生什麼事？我會把這個指令貼到這裡，讓 tmux 有新工作階段。目前我正在嘗試建立的專案中。簡單來說，我就在這裡執行這個指令。你可以看到這就是我們擁有的。所以我們現在進入了 tmux 模式。現在我們要做的是嘗試用危險的跳過權限來執行 Claude。我打算在 tmux 模式裡做 Claude 工作階段。
So first thing first, here you can see that it's prompted saying that yes, running in the bypass permission mode.I'm just going to say yes, accept.And here you can see that we have our claw code sessions inside of this current project directory.
首先，你可以看到它會提示說「是的，正在略過權限模式下執行」。我就直接說好，接受。你可以看到我們在這個目前專案目錄中有 Claude Code 的工作階段。
All right, so now once we have the setups done and also the overview, now let's take a look at how we can reuse it, how we can reuse the agent teams inside of our projects to basically start it up, be able to manage it, be able to shut it down, be able to build our projects using agent teams.So in this case, I'm just going to come back to my terminal here.And what I'm going to do here is I'm just going to copy this prompt and paste it into claw code.And here is what this prompt says.
好了，現在在完成設定和概述後，接下來我們來看看如何重用這些技術，如何在專案中重用Agent Teams，基本上是啟動、管理、關閉，並用Agent Teams來建立我們的專案。所以在這種情況下，我就回到我的終端機。我現在要做的是，我會把這個提示詞複製並貼到 Claude Code 裡。以下是這個提示詞所說的內容。
So basically the goal is we want to research the direct bank connection
所以基本上我們的目標是研究直接銀行連結
either through these providers right here and that will can be able to automatically import transactions into our applications and that's the goal and basically what we want to do here is that this the keyword is to create a team and basically if you were to look at documentation on how to trigger the agent teams all we have to do here to specify the create a agent teams to explore to build something to research something right that will basically trigger the agent team here to run it automatically in your cloud code no slash commands just the keyword on create a agent teams or create
透過這些提供者，我們就能自動將交易匯入我們的應用程式，這也是我們的目標。基本上我們想做的是，關鍵字是建立一個團隊，基本上如果你查看如何觸發Agent Teams的文件，我們只要在這裡指定「建立Agent Teams」來探索並建立一些東西要研究正確的東西，基本上會觸發Agent Teams自動在你的 Claude Code 中執行，沒有斜杠指令，只要關鍵字在「建立Agent Teams」或「創建」上
team so here you can see I just said I create a team called this four parallel agents and after they complete the jobs we'll basically aggregate the findings into this MD file right here and I also have give a reference to Jira ticket so they can trigger the Jira MCP server to pull the context about what the ticket is about and here you can see that we have our different agents we have our business agents we have our financial agents technical architectures and devil advocates let's go through them one by one so here you can see that we have our agent one here so what I have here for the format is that I have a name I have a model and I also have
團隊：你可以看到，我剛剛說我創建了一個團隊，叫做四個平行代理，完成工作後，我們會把結果彙整到這個 MD 檔案中，我也提供了 Jira 工單的參考，讓他們能觸發 Jira MCP 伺服器，拉取工單的上下文，這裡你可以看到我們有不同的代理有我們的商業代理人，有我們的財務代理人、技術架構和魔鬼代言人。我們逐一介紹，這裡你可以看到我們有代理人，這裡有我的代理人。格式是我有一個名字，有一個模型，我也有一個
Now, of course, I've also made a video here on top of how you can be able to create your own sub-agents for different situations in your application building.Now, of course, if you want to learn more about sub-agents, you can check out this video right here where you can learn more about how sub-agent works, how you can create your sub-agents, and basically what you can do with your sub-agents, right?So what I did here is I specified the sub-agents that's going to be working on this task, right, for this agents, focusing on the business and products.
當然，我也在這裡製作了一支影片，說明你如何在應用程式建置中針對不同情境創建自己的子代理。當然，如果你想更了解子代理，可以看看這支影片，了解子代理的運作方式、如何創建子代理，以及基本上你可以用子代理做些什麼，對吧？所以我在這裡指定了將負責這項任務的子代理，對，針對這些代理，專注於業務和產品。
And the goal here is that it's going to use the web search here to gather the competitor and the market data and it's going to analyze it, right, try to analyze thecompetitors, try to see what are the market fit look like, the user experience, the impact analysis, and try to aggregate those results.And that's what the agent one is trying to do.And we also have our agent two here, which focuses on the financial cost.So which provider we're going to use and what is the cost for that?
目標是利用網路搜尋來收集競爭對手和市場數據，並嘗試分析這些數據，看看市場契合度、使用者體驗、影響分析，並嘗試彙整這些結果。而這正是代理一想要做的事。我們這裡還有 Agent 2，專注於財務成本。那我們要用哪家供應商？費用是多少？
And we're going to have a cost projection here table to show that.And that's basically Agent 2 for the financial and cost.And then the Agent 3 here is the technical architecture.And notice here that I also changed the model here to be Opus because the work that Agent 3 completes here is gonna be very complex.So that's why I assigned the system architect sub-agent here for the Opus model with the technical architecture.We're gonna architecture this project by using the abstraction layer.Basically it means that it doesn't matter which provider we're gonna use, right?
我們這裡會有一個成本預測表來展示這點。這基本上就是 Agent 2 的財務和成本。而這裡的 Agent 3 則是技術架構。注意這裡我也把模型改成 Opus，因為 Agent 3 在這裡完成的工作會非常複雜。所以我指派系統架構師子代理，負責 Opus 模型與技術架構。我們將透過抽象層來架構這個專案。基本上，這代表我們用哪家服務提供商都沒差，對吧？
we're just going to create extraction similar to a repository pattern where the application here is going to call that repository or call that extraction layer for the service let's say in the future we're going to switch from playing to Flink simply just changing that service in the config or simply just changing that in the repository and it will basically affect that from all the applications that will basically use that providers right so we're creating abstraction layer to abstract the dependencies for different providers we're going to use and that's why we have it here okay and here you can see that I also mentioned we're going to use a mermay diagram here for the architecture
我們會建立類似儲存庫模式的擷取，應用程式會呼叫該儲存庫或抽象層，未來我們會從 Plaid 切換到 Flinks 的設定檔或儲存庫中的設定，這基本上會影響所有使用該服務提供者的應用程式我們正在建立抽象層來抽象不同供應商的相依關係，這也是為什麼我們會在這裡設置它，好，你可以看到我也提到我們會用 Mermaid 圖來做架構
overview and these are the skills we're going to trigger and these are sub agents that we can have right so you can see that we have our agent three now agent one and three here you can see that they are all standalone agents which means that they don't have to communicate to each other because you know they're all working on their own task but for agent four here I specifically mentioned that you can be able to communicate to each agents here directly and basically this agent here is a general purpose agent is basically act as a devil advocate it's going to challenge stress test any findings from agents one to three for any task that it's trying to do so that's basically the
概述，這些是我們將要觸發的 skill，這些是我們可以設置的子代理。你可以看到，我們有代理三，現在代理一和代理三，可以看到它們都是獨立代理，這表示他們不需要彼此溝通，因為他們各自在執行自己的任務。但對於代理四，我特別提到了你可以直接與每位代理人溝通，基本上這位代理人是通用代理人，扮演魔鬼代言人的角色，會對代理人一到三的發現進行壓力測試，針對它嘗試執行的任何任務，這基本上就是
four agents that I'm going to spin up and this is the entire prompt and lastly we also have our lead which is basically our tech lead that spin up those four sub agents here to do the work and at the end of it it's going to aggregate the data and be able to conclude everything like the followings so basically that's my prompt and what I'm going to do here is I'm going to copy this come back to my terminal and I'm just going to paste it right here all right so then in this case I'm just going to run this and let's take a look at what it does all right so now you can see it's going to set up the research team here first take a look at the Jira ticket by calling the Jira MC server all right so once we have
我會啟動四個代理，這是整個提示詞，最後還有我們的 Team Lead，會啟動這四個子代理來執行工作，最後它會彙整資料並能夠像以下這樣總結所有內容。基本上這就是我的提示詞，我接下來要做的是要複製這個，回到我的終端機，我會直接貼到這裡。好，在這種情況下，我會執行這個，讓我們看看它做了什麼。現在你可以看到它會在這裡設置研究團隊，先透過呼叫 Jira MCP 伺服器來查看 Jira 工單。好，一旦我們有了
the full context from both Jira and the existing backlog, now it's going to create a team and spin up four research agents.So here you can see it's going to create the four agent teams, basically try to set up the tiles tracking, spin up all four research agents here in parallel.All right, so now you can see that we have two sub-agents here spin up.One is the business products, the other one is the financial cost.And we can literally just type in anything here inside of those sub-agents here to communicate.
Jira和現有積壓的完整背景，現在要組建團隊並啟動四名研究代理。這裡你可以看到它會建立四個 Agent Teams，基本上嘗試設置圖塊追蹤，並同時啟動四個研究代理。好，現在你可以看到我們這裡有兩個子代理正在啟動。一是商業產品，另一是財務成本。我們甚至可以直接在這裡輸入這些子代理內的任何東西來溝通。
And here you can see it's going to spin up another sub-agent here called the technical architect.which is going to do the work and I could be typing anything here to communicate with the different sub-agents.And lastly, we also have our devil advocate here, got spin up, which will basically question everything that the agent here is trying to do.Now, if I want to switch to between here, you simply just use the keyboard here to do the Ctrl+B.So you can see Ctrl+B.I can switch over to the main chatbot here.I can tab.
你可以看到它會啟動另一個子代理，叫做技術架構師，負責執行工作，我可以在這裡打字，與不同的子代理溝通。最後，我們還有魔鬼代言人也已啟動，基本上會質疑代理人所做的一切。現在，如果我想切換到這裡，你只要用鍵盤按 Ctrl+B，這樣你就能看到 Ctrl+B。我可以切換到主聊天機器人。我可以打tab。
Here is what I have to check on the devil advocate's progress.If I want to switch over to specific agent, for example, I want to switch over to the architecture, I just do Ctrl+B.You can see that at the bottom here changed the architecture design.So now if I were to type, you can see that I have switched over to the architecture.I can also switch over to the green side, which you can see here.So the hidden bank interaction cost by using the Ctrl+B up arrow and down arrow, simply just looking at this, it'll switch it over.
以下是我必須檢查的魔鬼代言人進度。如果我想切換到特定的代理，例如，我想切換到架構，我只要按 Ctrl+B。你可以在這裡看到底部修改了架構設計。所以如果我打字，你可以看到我已經切換到架構模式。我也可以切換到綠色那一面，你可以在這裡看到。所以透過 Ctrl+B 的上箭頭和下箭頭，只要看這個，隱藏的銀行互動成本就會切換。
I can also shift it over to the open bank research questions.I can also be able to say things like, Hey, how's it going?How's it going?I can be able to interact with this agent.But clearly, if you just want to follow through instead of here in the terminal, I can just control B left, and it'll basically navigate me here to the root, which here you can see I can be able to talk to the main agent here, the orchestrator, which will basically orchestrate the entire thing.
我也可以把它轉移到開放銀行研究問題。我也可以說像是「嘿，最近怎麼樣？」這樣的話。最近怎麼樣？我可以和這位代理互動。但很明顯，如果你只是想在終端機裡直接執行，而不是這裡，我只要按 Ctrl+B 左鍵，它就會直接帶我到根源，你可以看到我可以跟主代理——編排器溝通，它基本上會幫你編排整個流程。
So in this case, I'm just going to wait for a bit until everything.synthesizing for the final research reports.So now you can see eventually we have the entire research has complete.And if I want to scroll up and down, simply just do control B and using the square bracket, the left square bracket, it'll basically help you to scroll up and down.So you can see I was able to scroll up and down here to figure out, okay, what has been done.
所以這次我打算等一陣子，直到所有東西合成完成，準備最終的研究報告。所以你可以看到，最終我們完成了整個研究。如果我想上下捲動，只要按控制B，然後用方括號（左方括號），基本上就能幫助你上下捲動。所以你可以看到我能夠在這裡上下滑動，找出，好吧，已經做了什麼。
So we have the output files, the agent one, the agent two, the results, and we also have the research and here we also have the entire research summary and all the files have been addedit, which we can see here.So pretty much that's how we can use the agent team here to start it, to manage it, to complete it.So in this case, let's take a look at what the result look like by simply now getting to VS Code.And I'm just going to open this in preview here.And here you can see that this is our final report.
我們有輸出檔案，代理人一號、代理人二號、結果，還有研究資料，這裡還有完整的研究摘要，所有檔案都已新增，我們可以在這裡看到。所以基本上這就是我們利用Agent Teams來啟動、管理並完成它的方式。所以在這種情況下，讓我們來看看現在進入 VS Code 後的結果是什麼樣子。我現在就在這裡預覽一下。這裡你可以看到這是我們的最終報告。
So first thing first, you can see that we have our table of content.So we have our go or no go recommendations.So should we implement this feature or not implement this feature?And we also have the provider recommendations for using this feature, what is the cost breakdown,architecture if we're going to build this, the risk and also the implementation phases and the appendix and such.So here you can see the final reports.So we have what are the reasons why we should go with this because all the competitors are using this because this will save time for the consumers.
首先，你可以看到我們有目錄。所以我們有 Go/No-Go 建議。那麼，我們應該實作這個功能還是不實作？我們也有供應商對使用此功能的建議，包括成本細分、架構（如果要建置）、風險，以及實施階段和附錄等。所以你可以在這裡看到最終報告。所以我們有理由選擇這個方案，因為所有競爭對手都在使用這個方法，這樣可以為消費者節省時間。
then there's also the list of against so why we should not use this feature for example only 53% of the consumers comfortable sharing their financial data it can also be a barrier of entry for small platform like this right there's also the connection reliabilities and here is the provider recommendation after it has done the research so if we're going to only focus on Canada then that's going to be flanks if we're going to use the US expansions we might want to choose a different providers so pretty much this is the breakdown and here is the cost
還有反對清單，為什麼我們不應該使用這個功能？例如，只有53%的消費者願意分享他們的財務資料，這也可能成為小型平台的進入障礙。還有連線可靠性，這是供應商在做完研究後的建議。如果我們只專注於加拿大，那就是 Flinks，如果要用美國擴充，我們可能會想選擇其他供應商，所以大致上這就是價格的細分，費用如下
Here's the pricing.So stuff like this.So this is the provider strategy.So for the 1,000 user, maybe we're going to focus on Canadian first.And for 1,000 to 2,000, we're going to expand to US market.This is what we have here.Scale, so stuff like this.Why not use other providers?It gives you the reason.And here's the cost summary.So per provider cost at scale.So let's say your user only has two bank accounts.Roughly for 100 users, this is how much it will be charged.And because there is different tiers for playing where, oh, if you have more users,
這是價格。像這樣的事情。這就是提供者的策略。所以對於1,000名用戶，也許我們會先聚焦在加拿大。而對於1,000到2,000，我們會擴展到美國市場。這就是我們這裡的狀況。像是這種規模。為什麼不使用其他服務提供商？它給了你理由。這是費用摘要。所以在規模化時，每個提供者的成本。假設你的用戶只有兩個銀行帳戶。大約 100 位用戶會收取這樣的費用。而且因為 Plaid 有不同方案層級，喔，如果用戶數比較多，
Each user here is gonna pay less.So that's basically what you get here, okay?And of course, there's also the flanks here.So let's say if we only wanna focus on flanks, this is how much it costs, okay?So pretty much that's the comparison and the architecture recommendation here you can see, this is all the things that it creates for the abstraction layer.And also here you can see the database schema, right?The jobs, the connected accounts, ID.the expanded column here for the bank transactions, right?So stuff like this.
這裡的每位用戶都會付更少的費用。所以基本上這就是你在這裡得到的，好嗎？當然，這裡還有 Flinks。所以假設我們只想專注在 Flinks，這就是成本，好嗎？基本上這就是比較和架構建議，你可以看到，這些都是它為抽象層所創造的所有東西。這裡你也可以看到資料庫的結構，對吧？工作、連結帳戶、ID。這裡擴展的銀行交易欄位，對吧？像這樣的事情。
And there's also the bank connection providers here.So it has to scan through the documentations and try to create something like this that we're gonna use inside of our application, like disconnect, get account details, sync the connections, or refresh the authorizations here, stuff like that, okay?So pretty much that's pretty much the entire research.Overall, I won't go too much in detail here.There's also individual file, but pretty much that's how we can be able to use the agent teamsspin up multiple sub agents here to run it, to manage it, and be able to finish it.
這裡還有銀行連線供應商。所以它必須掃描文件，嘗試建立類似我們應用程式內的支援，比如斷線、取得帳號詳細資料、同步連線，或重新整理授權，類似這樣的操作，好嗎？所以基本上這就是整個研究的重點。總的來說，我這裡就不打算多說了。也有個別檔案，但基本上這就是我們能利用Agent Teams，組建多個子代理來管理、執行並完成它的方式。
Alright, so lastly, what I want to talk about is basically how you can convert everything here into a claw skill, because running this could be challenging, right?You tell us what to do, what to research, and you have to write a long prompt just like what you see here.
好，最後我想談的是，基本上要把這裡的一切轉換成 Claude skill，因為執行這些可能會很有挑戰性，對吧？你告訴我們該做什麼、該研究什麼，還得寫一個很長的提示詞，就像你看到的那樣。
And so instead of like creating a claw skills from scratch by simply just prompting it, what I recommend to do is that after you finish the entire run, which here you can see this is the entire run, and all I have to do here just basically prompted the claw here after I finish a session, and I'm just simply going to say, based onthis conversation that we have, can you create a skill that I can be able to reuse it in the future?
所以我建議你，與其像從零開始創造 Claude skill 那樣，只要直接提示它，我建議你完成整個流程後，這裡你可以看到這是整個流程，我只要在一個工作階段結束後，直接提示 Claude 就行了， 我只想說，根據我們這次的對話，你能不能創造一個 skill，讓我未來能重複使用？
And simply all I had to do here just pass the parameter on exactly what's the research topic or what's the Jira ticket.And simply you can be able to run it and be able to find the context or be able to give the research idea here like what we just set up today with four sub agents.Can you create a skill?And that's basically my prompt.And I'm just going to run this and have it to basically create a skill based on this current conversation that we just went through.Alright, so now you can see that after it has
我在這裡只要傳遞一個參數，告訴我研究主題或 Jira 的票據是什麼。而且你可以直接執行，找到背景，或像我們今天用四個子代理設置的那樣，提出研究想法。你能創造 skill 嗎？這基本上就是我的題目。我會執行這個，基本上是根據我們剛剛討論的這段對話，創造一個 skill。好，現在你可以看到它已經發生了
create the skill, this is basically how we can use it.We simply just do slash research team and we basically put the ticket number, right, for the Jira ticket, or we can also be able to specify that in the free text mode.There's also the custom output directories, so stuff like this.We can be able to use that.Literally, I can be able to use a test topic here and do that.
創造 skill，基本上就是我們能用它的方式。我們只要執行 /research-team，基本上就是把 Jira 工單的工單號碼輸入，或者也可以在自由文字模式下指定。還有自訂輸出目錄，類似這樣的功能。我們可以利用這點。我真的可以用測試主題來做這件事。
So pretty much that's how we can be able to reuse it by simply just building a skill and be able to spin up those four sub-agents that we just mentioned.And if you actually want to learn more about the skill, you can click on the skill, click on the research team that you just created, and clearly you can see that we have the four agents here.So phase one is going to be research, spin up three sub-agents with fresh context, and we also have the challenge here, which is the advocates.
所以基本上，我們只要建立一個 skill，就能重用它，並啟動剛才提到的那四個子代理。如果你真的想了解更多關於這項 skill 的資訊，可以點擊這個 skill，點擊你剛建立的研究團隊，很明顯你可以看到我們這裡有四位代理。所以第一階段將是研究，啟動三個帶有新上下文的子代理，同時我們也有挑戰，那就是魔鬼代言人。
basically try to read through all the research file and challenge the assumptions.And then the phase three here is reading through all four files, write a final report.So pretty much that's how it works.We put everything into a scale so that we can easily just reuse that going forward.Alright, so pretty much that's it for this video.In this video, we went over what is agent teams, how's it different compared to like sub agents and the default mode and what is the problem that agent teams trying to solve.
基本上就是試著閱讀所有研究文件，並挑戰這些假設。第三階段是閱讀全部四個檔案，撰寫最終報告。大致上就是這樣運作的。我們把所有東西都做成一個 skill，這樣未來就能輕鬆重複使用。好了，這支影片大致就到這裡。在這支影片中，我們介紹了什麼是 Agent Teams、它與子代理有何不同、預設模式，以及 Agent Teams 試圖解決的問題是什麼。
as well as how we can be able to set up the Asian teams here using T-Max and also how we can be able to start a session, manage a session, and also shut down the session as well.And eventually we can be able to create a claw scale here to reuse this going forward without us having to repetitively...communicate to each individual sub-agents here to do so.
以及我們如何利用 tmux 來設置 Agent Teams，以及如何開始一個工作階段、管理一個工作階段，甚至關閉該工作階段。最終我們可以在這裡製作一個 Claude skill，未來可以重複使用這些，而不必反覆......請與這裡的每位子代理溝通以達成此目的。
So pretty much that's it for this video and if you do familiar with this video, please make sure to like this video, consider subscribing for more content like this, and I'll make sure to put the entire guide on how to do this inside of the school community so you can be able to copy this and run on your local machine step by step.So with that being said, thank you very much for watching and I'll see you in this video.
大致上這支影片就到這裡，如果你喜歡這支影片，請務必按讚，並考慮訂閱更多類似的內容，我也會把整個教學指南放進學校社群，讓你能逐步複製並執行在本地機器上。所以說到這裡，非常感謝你的收看，我們會在這段影片中見。